<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A New Testament Greek Course Based Inspired by Pharr</title>
    <link>https://amindforlanguage.com/pharrbook/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A New Testament Greek Course Based Inspired by Pharr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amindforlanguage.com/pharrbook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://amindforlanguage.com/pharrbook/posts/lesson_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amindforlanguage.com/pharrbook/posts/lesson_0/</guid>
      <description>This book is an introduction to New Testament Greek.
It aims to teach Greek through reading John&amp;rsquo;s Gospel, and learning grammar and vocabulary as needed to read, really read, the Greek text. John has a relatively low number of vocabulary items https://amindforlanguage.com/greek/2022/08/23/john-stats.html to learn but is long enough to expose learners to a good deal of content.
One unique feature of this book is that as soon as possible the discussions about Greek will begin to be written in Greek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 1: Greek nouns</title>
      <link>https://amindforlanguage.com/pharrbook/posts/lesson_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amindforlanguage.com/pharrbook/posts/lesson_1/</guid>
      <description>Greek words change form to show their function in a sentence and to tell us what or who they refer to.
This is true of nouns which are the topic of this lesson.
γραμματική (Grammar) Nouns are what we talk about.
A noun is a person, place, thing, or idea. The Greek word for a noun is ὄνομα, which literally means &amp;rsquo;name&#39;.
Greek nouns change their ending to show:
how many things they refer to (known as ἀριθμός or number), and to show their role in the sentence (known as πτῶσις or case) New Testament Greek has three ἀριθμοἰ: ἀριθμοί is the plural of ἀριθμός.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
